{
    "PU": [
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (8 + 10i) + (9 + 1i)",
            "correct_answer": "17.0 + 11.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.06, Argument: 30\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 10 + 3i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 5i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 5.39, Argument: 68\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -3 + -10i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -4 + 9i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 3i) + (3 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "13.0 + 12.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 3 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "5.0(cos(53\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(53\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 9 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 13.45, Argument: 48\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 3(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "4.5 + 7.79i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 2(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + -3.46i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 3(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-4.5 + 7.79i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -10 + 8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 10 + 1i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.05, Argument: 6\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -9 + 8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (5 + 3i) + (1 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "6.0 + 12.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 4.34(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "2.17 + 3.76i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (8 + 10i) / (6 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "1.18 + -0.1i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 8 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.94, Argument: 27\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 3 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 4.24, Argument: 45\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.62, Argument: 23\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 1i) * (5 + 7i)",
            "correct_answer": "13.0 + 33.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 4 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.94, Argument: 63\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 2(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-8.0 + -13.86i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (6 + 9i) + (10 + 1i)",
            "correct_answer": "16.0 + 10.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 1(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 1.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (8 + 6i) - (10 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + -3.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.9, Argument: 45\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 2(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "2.0 + 3.46i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 2(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + 3.46i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 4.1(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "2.05 + 3.55i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -4 + -7i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 2(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + 3.46i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 7 + 9i",
            "correct_answer": "11.4(cos(52\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(52\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (8 + 10i) + (3 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "11.0 + 14.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.33(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 1.33i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -3 + 7i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -2 + 10i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -3 + -4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 4(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-64.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 5i) / (4 + 10i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.57 + -0.17i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 5(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2209.71 + -2209.71i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 3 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 6.71, Argument: 63\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 1i) + (8 + 3i)",
            "correct_answer": "9.0 + 4.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 2(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-27.71 + 16.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 6 + 1i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 6.08, Argument: 9\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 1(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 2(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 8.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 2(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + -3.46i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 4i) - (3 + 5i)",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 1 + 9i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.06, Argument: 84\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 4 + -8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 3(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-171.83 + -171.83i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 8 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 12.81, Argument: 51\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (2 + 10i) * (1 + 7i)",
            "correct_answer": "-68.0 + 24.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 4(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 1024.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 5 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "9.43(cos(58\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(58\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 10 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "12.81(cos(39\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(39\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 4(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-8.0 + 13.86i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.2, Argument: 79\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 5 + 10i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 7 + 4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -2 + 10i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 4i) / (5 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.42 + 0.13i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 4i) / (6 + 10i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.74 + -0.56i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 3(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-4.5 + -7.79i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 5i) * (2 + 5i)",
            "correct_answer": "-23.0 + 15.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -8 + 7i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 9 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 13.45, Argument: 48\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 2.45(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 2.45i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 5 + 2i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -5 + -1i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 10 + -4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -2 + 8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 4.88(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2.44 + 4.23i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 6 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 11.66, Argument: 59\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 6 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.49, Argument: 45\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.3(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-0.65 + 1.13i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (6 + 1i) / (10 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.6 + -0.02i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 5.39, Argument: 22\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        }
    ],
    "CET": [
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.98(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 1.98i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 7 + 5i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 5i) + (7 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "8.0 + 9.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 3 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.62, Argument: 67\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 10 + -1i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 8 + 2i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 4.02(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "2.84 + 2.84i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 4.47, Argument: 63\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 7 + 0i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "Axis",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 1(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 2 + 5i",
            "correct_answer": "5.39(cos(68\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(68\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 9i) / (6 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "1.32 + -0.26i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 9 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.49, Argument: 18\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 1 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "7.07(cos(82\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(82\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 3 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 6.71, Argument: 63\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 4 + 1i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 4.12, Argument: 14\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 9i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 11.4, Argument: 52\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 3 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "5.0(cos(53\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(53\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 6 + 9i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.82, Argument: 56\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (5 + 2i) - (9 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "-4.0 + -7.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.56(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "1.1 + 1.1i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 4 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.94, Argument: 63\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 10 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 14.14, Argument: 45\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -5 + 0i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "Axis",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.25, Argument: 76\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 8 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "11.31(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (9 + 5i) - (9 + 1i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 4.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 7 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "9.9(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 3.29(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "2.85 + 1.64i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 3.92(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-1.96 + 3.39i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 8 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "8.54(cos(21\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(21\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (5 + 8i) / (6 + 10i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.81 + -0.01i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 2.0(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "1.73 + 1.0i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 2(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-8.0 + 13.86i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.28, Argument: 16\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 1(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-0.5 + 0.87i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (6 + 3i) / (6 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.6 + -0.3i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 6 + 10i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 3 + -8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 1 + 8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 5(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "125.0 + -0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 0 + 2i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "Axis",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 10 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "12.81(cos(39\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(39\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 5(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-88.39 + 88.39i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -5 + -5i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 8 + 1i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.06, Argument: 7\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 2(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-2.0 + -3.46i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 2.45(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-1.22 + 2.12i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 6 + -2i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 6 + 4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -3 + 2i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -5 + -8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 3(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-40.5 + 70.15i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 9 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 13.45, Argument: 48\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (7 + 7i) / (10 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.81 + 0.54i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (5 + 8i) / (6 + 6i)",
            "correct_answer": "1.08 + 0.25i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.6, Argument: 54\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (6 + 10i) * (3 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "-22.0 + 54.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (5 + 7i) / (5 + 5i)",
            "correct_answer": "1.2 + 0.2i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 2 + 6i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -9 + -7i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 8 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.25, Argument: 14\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 6 + 0i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "Axis",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.81, Argument: 50\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 1 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.05, Argument: 84\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 3(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 9.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 9 + 4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.28, Argument: 16\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (9 + 10i) * (3 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "-13.0 + 66.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 9i) + (8 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "12.0 + 17.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 4(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 16.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (9 + 4i) - (7 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "2.0 + 2.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (6 + 7i) * (10 + 10i)",
            "correct_answer": "-10.0 + 130.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (7 + 5i) * (7 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "29.0 + 63.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.63, Argument: 49\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 2 + -3i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 10 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 11.66, Argument: 31\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 10i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.2, Argument: 79\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (7 + 1i) * (6 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "34.0 + 62.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 4(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 1024.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 2 + 4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -2 + -6i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 4(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-724.08 + -724.08i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 2.08(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 2.08i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 3(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 243.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 2i) - (4 + 7i)",
            "correct_answer": "6.0 + -5.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 3.23(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "1.62 + 2.8i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        }
    ],
    "JEE": [
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 4(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 64.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 7i) * (3 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "-26.0 + 101.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 4(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-128.0 + 221.7i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^2 where z = 5(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-12.5 + 21.65i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 10 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "10.2(cos(11\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(11\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 6 + 5i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.81, Argument: 40\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -3 + -7i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 3(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-0.0 + -27.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 9 + 5i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 10.3, Argument: 29\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -5 + 3i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 0 + -10i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "Axis",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 4 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 5.0, Argument: 37\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -6 + 6i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 5i) + (9 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "13.0 + 7.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.29(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.65 + 1.12i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 3 + 1i",
            "correct_answer": "3.16(cos(18\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(18\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 8i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.43, Argument: 58\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 3i) + (7 + 1i)",
            "correct_answer": "17.0 + 4.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 3 + 7i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 5(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-312.5 + 541.27i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 4 + 5i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 6.4, Argument: 51\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (3 + 1i) * (6 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "16.0 + 12.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 4 + -3i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 2 + -5i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 3(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "81.0 + -0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 7 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.9, Argument: 45\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 6 + 8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -1 + -6i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (9 + 8i) + (4 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "13.0 + 12.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 4.87(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "3.44 + 3.44i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 4(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "256.0 + -0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 10 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "10.2(cos(11\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(11\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.18(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.59 + 1.02i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 4(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-45.25 + 45.25i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -10 + -3i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -1 + 4i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "II",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 3(cos(60\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(60\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-40.5 + -70.15i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (2 + 1i) / (5 + 7i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.23 + -0.12i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 8i) + (4 + 4i)",
            "correct_answer": "5.0 + 12.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 6 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 6.32, Argument: 18\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -1 + -2i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 8i) / (8 + 7i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.78 + 0.32i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (8 + 6i) * (9 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "18.0 + 126.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 3.61, Argument: 56\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 5i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 7.07, Argument: 45\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 6i) / (8 + 3i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.68 + 0.49i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 7i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 8.6, Argument: 54\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (6 + 10i) / (9 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.92 + 0.29i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 3 + 9i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.49, Argument: 72\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 2 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 6.32, Argument: 72\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 2th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 8 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "8.54(cos(21\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(21\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 5.83, Argument: 31\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 3.2(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-1.6 + 2.77i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 9 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "10.82(cos(34\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(34\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (9 + 1i) + (2 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "11.0 + 9.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 5(cos(120\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(120\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "125.0 + -0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 5(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-0.0 + -125.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (2 + 10i) / (4 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "1.4 + 1.8i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 7i) + (10 + 9i)",
            "correct_answer": "11.0 + 16.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^4 where z = 2(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-8.0 + 13.86i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 4 + -3i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "IV",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 9 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 9.85, Argument: 24\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (1 + 2i) - (5 + 2i)",
            "correct_answer": "-4.0 + 0.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (3 + 7i) - (4 + 3i)",
            "correct_answer": "-1.0 + 4.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 6th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + -0.87i, 0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (10 + 5i) * (6 + 8i)",
            "correct_answer": "20.0 + 110.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the modulus and argument of 5 + 2i",
            "correct_answer": "Modulus: 5.39, Argument: 22\u00b0",
            "topic": "Modulus and Argument"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (9 + 2i) + (8 + 5i)",
            "correct_answer": "17.0 + 7.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 3 + 6i",
            "correct_answer": "6.71(cos(63\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(63\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (7 + 9i) * (7 + 3i)",
            "correct_answer": "22.0 + 84.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -2 + 0i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "Axis",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number 6 + 5i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "I",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 3th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, -0.5 + 0.87i, -0.5 + -0.87i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 1.03(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 1.03i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^3 where z = 1(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-0.71 + 0.71i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 3 + 3i",
            "correct_answer": "4.24(cos(45\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(45\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (8 + 3i) / (10 + 6i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.72 + -0.13i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 8th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.71 + 0.71i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -0.71 + 0.71i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.71 + -0.71i, -0.0 + -1.0i, 0.71 + -0.71i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 8 + 4i",
            "correct_answer": "8.94(cos(27\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(27\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Plot the complex number -9 + -8i on the Argand plane. Which quadrant does it lie in?",
            "correct_answer": "III",
            "topic": "Argand Plane"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find z^5 where z = 4(cos(30\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(30\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "-886.81 + 512.0i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the 4th roots of unity.",
            "correct_answer": "1.0 + 0.0i, 0.0 + 1.0i, -1.0 + 0.0i, -0.0 + -1.0i",
            "topic": "Roots of Unity"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to cartesian: 4.57(cos(90\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(90\u00b0))",
            "correct_answer": "0.0 + 4.57i",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Convert to polar: 9 + 1i",
            "correct_answer": "9.06(cos(6\u00b0) + i\u00b7sin(6\u00b0))",
            "topic": "Polar-Cartesian Conversion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Simplify: (4 + 3i) / (8 + 1i)",
            "correct_answer": "0.54 + 0.31i",
            "topic": "Miscellaneous"
        }
    ]
}